Finding aid for Library (University of Michigan) Records, 1837 - 2013
Bentley Historical Library
- Deputy Director's Office, 1980-1991
  - Topical Files, 1980-2005
    - 1980-1998, 1989-1998
      - Library Staff Advisory Committee (LSAC): Elections, 1993-1998 (Box 252)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (LSA) Library Committee (Box 253)
        - 1980-1989, 2 folders (Box 253)
        - 1990-1991 (Box 253)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 253)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 253)
      - Making of America (MOA), 1994-1995 (Box 253)
      - Memoir of a Book, 1989-1997 (Box 253)
      - Michigan Center for the Book
        - 1988-1989 (Box 253)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 253)
      - M-Link, 1987-1995; 2 folders (Box 253)
      - National Commission on Libraries and Information Sciences, 1990-1993 (Box 253)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH), 1989-1990; 1994 (Box 253)
      - Papyri Proposal, 1987 (Box 253)
      - Photoduplication
        - 1989-1992 (Box 253)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 253)
      - Planning Guide, 1982-1983 (Box 253)
      - Point of Intersection Reports, 1988; 1990 (Box 253)
      - Press Releases
        - 1988-1989 (Box 253)
        - 1990 (Box 253)
        - 1991 (Box 253)
        - 1992 (Box 253)
        - 1993 (Box 253)
        - 1994 (Box 253)
      - Provost and Vice President for Academic Affairs (Box 254)
        - 1989-1993, 2 folders (Box 254)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 254)
        - 1995-1996 (Box 254)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 254)
        - 1997-1998 (Box 254)
      - Shelf Reliability Team Final Report, 1994-1995; 2 folders (Box 254)
      - Staff Manual, 1992; 2 folders (Box 254)
      - Undergraduate Library (UGLi) Renovation (note: a short report on the UGLi's 30th anniversary is included in the file), 1983-1992 (scattered) (Box 254)
      - University Press, 1989-1993 (Box 254)
    - 1998-1999
      - Acquisitions (Box 290)
      - Administrative Meeting (Box 254)
      - Alternative Press (Box 254)
      - American Library Association (ALA) (Box 254)
      - Ameritech (Box 254)
      - Area Programs (Box 254)
      - Asia Library (Box 254)
      - Assessment (Box 254)
      - Association of College and Research Libraries (ACRL) (Box 254)
      - Association of Research Libraries (ARL)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 254)
        - Board of Directors (Box 254)
        - Scholarly Publishing and Resources Coalition (SPARC) (Box 254)
        - Statistics (Box 254)
      - Attorney (Box 254)
      - Awards Committee (Box 254)
      - Blackwell (Box 254)
      - Book Sale (Box 254)
      - Book Trouble (Box 254)
      - Buhr (Box 254)
      - Business and Finance Department (Box 254)
      - Cabinet (Box 254)
      - Café Shapiro (Box 254)
      - Center for Research Libraries (CRL)
        - General (Box 254)
        - Nominating Committee (Box 254)
      - Classification Evaluation Committee (CEC) (Box 254)
      - Clements Library (Box 290)
      - Coalition for Networked Information (CNI) (Box 255)
      - Collection Management and Development Committee/Council (CMDC) (Box 255)
      - Collections (Box 255)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC)
        - General, 4 folders (Box 255)
        - Directors (Box 255)
      - Communications, Press Releases, and Grants (Box 255)
      - Compensation Study (Box 255)
      - Cooperative Access System (CAS) (Box 255)
      - Copyrights (Box 255)
      - Correspondence: General (Box 290)
      - Council of State and University Library Directors (COLD) (Box 255)
      - Council on Library and Information Resources (CLIR): National Digital Library Federation (NDLF), 2 folders (Box 255)
      - DELPHI Group (Box 255)
      - Dentistry Library (Box 255)
      - Development (Box 256)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 256)
        - Library Friends (Box 256)
        - Visitors Tour (Box 256)
      - Digital Library Initiative (DLI)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 256)
        - Joint Planning Committee (Box 256)
        - JSTOR (Box 256)
      - Director's Update (Box 256)
      - Distance Education (Box 256)
      - Diversity (Box 256)
      - Diversity Committee (Box 256)
      - Emeritus Librarians (Box 256)
      - Equipment (Box 256)
      - Exchange and Gifts (Box 256)
      - Executive Council (Box 256)
      - Facilities (Box 256)
      - Faxon (Box 256)
      - Future of the Faculty Retreat (Box 256)
      - Graduate School (Rackham): Fellows (Box 256)
      - Grievance Procedure (Box 256)
      - Hatcher Graduate Library (Box 256)
      - Hatcher Renovations (Box 256)
      - Health Sciences Cluster (Box 256)
      - Human Resources (HR) (Box 290)
      - Information, School of (SI)
        - General (Box 256)
        - Class Presentation -- William Gosling (Box 256)
      - Information Technology Division (ITD) (Box 256)
      - Information Technology Strategic Directions Group (ITSDG) (Box 256)
      - Integrated Postsecondary Education Data System (IPEDS) (Box 256)
      - Interlibrary Loan (ILL) (Box 256)
      - International Federation of Library Associations and Institutions (IFLA) (Box 256)
      - Librarian Classification and Promotion Process (Box 256)
      - Librarian's Forum (Box 256)
      - Libraries Advisory Committee (LAC) (Box 256)
      - Library Council (Box 256)
      - Library of Congress (LOC) (Box 256)
      - Library of Michigan (Box 256)
      - Library Orientation (Box 256)
      - Library Staff Advisory Committee (LSAC) (Box 257)
        - General (Box 257)
        - Elections (Box 257)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (LSA) Visiting Committee (Box 257)
      - Media Rights Task Force (Box 257)
      - Media Union, 2 folders (Box 257)
      - Michigan Academic Library Strategic Plan (Box 257)
      - Michigan Electronic Library (MEL) (Box 257)
      - Michigan Library Association (MLA)
        - General (Box 257)
        - Awards (Box 257)
      - Michigan Research Libraries Triangle (MRLT)
        - General (Box 257)
        - Strategic Plan (Box 257)
      - Michigan, University of (Box 257)
      - MIRLYN (Box 257)
      - M-Link (Box 257)
      - M-Pathways (Box 257)
      - Music Library (Box 257)
      - Online Computer Library Center (OCLC) (Box 257)
      - Papyrology (Box 257)
      - Photoduplication (Box 257)
      - Pierpont Commons Working Group (Box 257)
      - Planning Retreat (Box 257)
      - Policy (Box 257)
      - Preservation/Conservation (Box 257)
      - Project Management Lead Team (PMLT) (Box 257)
      - Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (Box 257)
      - Public Services (Box 257)
      - Questionnaires (Box 257)
      - Research Libraries Group (RLG)
        - General (Box 257)
        - Electronic Mail (Box 257)
        - General Correspondence (Box 257)
        - Member Representative (Box 257)
        - RLIN (Box 257)
      - Residents (Box 257)
      - Science Library (Box 257)
      - Social Work Library (Box 257)
      - Special Collections Library (Box 257)
      - Staff Development (Box 257)
      - Systems (Box 257)
      - Taubman Medical Library (Box 257)
      - Technical Access Systems Services (TASS) (Box 257)
      - Travel Committee (Box 257)
      - University Press (Box 257)
      - Victor Vaughan Society (Box 257)
      - Visitors (Box 257)
      - Web Environment Working Group (Box 257)
    - 1999-2000
      - Accreditation Meeting (Box 257)
      - Acquisitions (Box 257)
      - Area Programs (Box 257)
      - Asia Library (Box 257)
      - Assessment (Box 257)
      - Association of Research Libraries (ARL)
        - General (Box 257)
        - Research Collections Committee (Box 257)
        - Scholarly Publishing and Resources Coalition (Box 257)
        - Statistics (Box 257)
      - Atkinson Award (Box 257)
      - Awards Committee (Box 257)
      - Baldwin, Ralph H. (Box 257)
      - Bentley Historical Library (Box 257)
      - Buhr (Box 257)
      - Business and Finance Department (Box 257)
      - Cabinet (Box 257)
      - Center for Research Libraries (CRL) (Box 257)
      - Classification Evaluation Committee (CEC) (Box 257)
      - Clements Library (Box 258)
        - Budget (Box 258)
        - Collections (Box 258)
        - Committee of Management, 2 folders (Box 258)
        - Personnel (Box 290)
        - Recon (Box 258)
      - Coalition of Networked Information (CNI) (Box 258)
      - Collection Management and Development Committee/Council (CMDC) (Box 258)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC)
        - General (Box 258)
        - Directors Files (Box 258)
      - Communications, Press Releases, and Grants (Box 258)
      - Cooperative Access System (CAS) (Box 258)
      - Copyrights (Box 258)
      - Council of State and University Library Directors (COLD) (Box 258)
      - Council on Library and Information Resources (CLIR)
        - General (Box 258)
        - National Digital Library Federation (NDLF), 2 folders (Box 258)
      - Detroit 300 (Box 258)
      - Development
        - General, 3 folders (Box 258)
        - Library Friends (Box 258)
      - Digital Library Initiative (DLI) (Box 259)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 259)
        - Joint Planning Group (Box 259)
        - JSTOR (Box 259)
      - Diversity (Box 259)
      - Diversity Committee (Box 259)
      - Dougherty Symposium, 2 folders (Box 259)
      - Early English Books Online (EEBO), 2 folders (Box 259)
      - EBSCO Speech (Box 259)
      - Executive Council (Box 259)
      - Facilities (Box 259)
      - Fellows (Box 259)
      - Florida, New York, and Washington, D.C. Development Trips (Box 259)
      - Hatcher Renovation (Box 259)
      - Human Resources (HR) (Box 259)
      - Information, School of (SI) (Box 259)
      - Information Technology Division (ITD) (Box 259)
      - Information Technology Strategic Directions Group (ITSDG) (Box 259)
      - Interlibrary Loan (ILL) (Box 259)
      - Internet 2 (Box 259)
      - Legal (Box 259)
      - Librarian's Forum (Box 259)
      - Libraries Advisory Committee (LAC) (Box 259)
      - Library Council (Box 259)
      - Library of Congress (LOC) (Box 259)
      - Library of Michigan (Box 259)
      - Library Orientation (Box 259)
      - Library Staff Advisory Committee (LSAC)
        - General (Box 259)
        - Elections (Box 259)
      - Media Union
        - General (Box 259)
        - Executive Committee (Box 259)
      - Michigan Electronic Library (MEL), 2 folders (Box 260)
      - Michigan Library Association (MLA) (Box 260)
      - Michigan Research Libraries Triangle (MRLT) (Box 260)
      - Michigan Virtual University (Box 260)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 260)
      - Music Library (Box 260)
      - New York Public Library -- Bibliotheque Nationale de France (Box 260)
      - Online Computer Library Center (OCLC) (Box 260)
      - Papyrology (Box 260)
      - Photoduplication Services (Box 260)
      - Preservation/Conservation (Box 260)
      - Pricing Electronic Access to Knowledge (PEAK) Conference (Box 260)
      - Printing (Box 260)
      - Promotion Review Committee (PRC) (Box 260)
      - Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (Box 260)
      - Public Goods Council
        - General (Box 260)
        - Alumni Magazine Issue (Box 260)
      - Public Health Library (Box 260)
      - Public Services (Box 260)
      - Reaccreditation (Box 260)
      - Research Libraries Group (RLG)
        - General (Box 260)
        - Collection Development and Resources Sharing (Box 260)
        - Electronic Mail (Box 260)
        - General Correspondence (Box 260)
        - Proposal (Box 260)
        - RLIN (Box 260)
      - Residents (Box 260)
      - Security Team (Box 260)
      - Shakespeare (Box 260)
      - Social Work Library (Box 260)
      - Spatial Analysis (Box 260)
      - Special Collections Library (Box 260)
      - Surveys (Box 260)
      - Taubman Medical Library (Box 260)
      - Technical Access Systems Services (TASS) (Box 260)
      - Travel Committee (Box 260)
      - Turner Lecture Series (Box 260)
      - Universitas 21 (Box 260)
      - University Press
        - General (Box 260)
        - Executive Committee (Box 260)
        - Finance Subcommittee (Box 260)
      - Vice-President for Research, Office of (OVPR) (Box 260)
      - Visitors (Box 260)
      - Whalls Endowment Fund (Box 260)
      - Y2K (Box 260)
    - 2000-2001
      - Access ER (electronic records) (Box 260)
      - Acquisitions (Box 260)
      - Administrative Meeting (Box 261)
      - Alternative Press (Box 261)
      - Ameritech (Box 261)
      - Amity Committee (Box 261)
      - Association of College and Research Libraries (ACRL): Excellence in Academic Libraries Award (Box 261)
      - Association of Research Libraries (ARL)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 261)
        - Board of Directors (Box 261)
        - Scholarly Publish and Resources Coalition (SPARC) (Box 261)
        - Statistics (Box 261)
      - Awards Committee (Box 261)
      - Bentley Historical Library (Box 261)
      - Booked for Breakfast (Box 261)
      - Book Sale (Box 261)
      - Buhr (Box 261)
      - Business Administration Library (Box 261)
      - Business and Finance Department (Box 261)
      - Cabinet Minutes (Box 261)
      - Center for Research Libraries (CRL) (Box 261)
      - Chalat Reception (Box 261)
      - Classification Evaluation Committee (CEC) (Box 261)
      - Clements Library
        - General (Box 261)
        - Budget (Box 261)
        - Committee of Management (Box 261)
        - Recon (Box 261)
      - Coffee with Faculty (Box 261)
      - Collections Management and Development Committee/Council (CMDC), 2 folders (Box 261)
      - Collections (Box 261)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC)
        - General (Box 261)
        - Center for Library Initiatives (CLI) (Box 261)
        - Directors Files, 2 folders (Box 261)
      - Communications, Public Relations, and Grants (Box 261)
      - Communications Task Force (Box 261)
      - Cooperative Access System (CAS) (Box 261)
      - Copyright Symposium (Box 261)
      - Copyrights (Box 261)
      - Council of State and University Library Directors (COLD) (Box 261)
      - Council on Library and Information Resources (CLIR)
        - General (Box 261)
        - National Digital Library Federation (NDLF) (Box 261)
      - Denver Alumni Club (Box 261)
      - Detroit 300 (Box 261)
      - Development (Box 262)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 262)
        - Library Friends (Box 262)
      - Digital Library Initiative
        - General, 2 folders (Box 262)
        - Elisevier (Box 262)
        - Information Technology (Box 262)
        - JSTOR (Box 262)
      - Director's Update (Box 262)
      - Diversity Committee (Box 262)
      - Early English Books Online (EEBO) (Box 262)
      - E-Books Conference (Box 262)
      - Executive Committee (Box 262)
      - Facilities (Box 262)
      - Fathom (Box 262)
      - Fellows (Box 262)
      - Field Librarians (Box 262)
      - Grievance Procedures (Box 262)
      - Hatcher Graduate Library
        - General (Box 262)
        - Renovation (Box 262)
      - Hilton, James (Box 262)
      - Human Resources (HR) (Box 262)
      - Information, School of (SI) (Box 262)
      - Information Technology Division (ITD) (Box 262)
      - Information Technology Strategic Directions Group (ITSDG) (Box 262)
      - Instructor College (Box 262)
      - Interlibrary Loan (ILL) (Box 262)
      - International Federation of Library Associations and Institutions (IFLA) (Box 262)
      - Law Library (Box 262)
      - Librarian's Forum (Box 262)
      - Libraries Advisory Committee (LAC) (Box 262)
      - Library Council (Box 263)
      - Library History (Box 263)
      - Library Logo (Box 263)
      - Library Management System (Box 263)
      - Library of Congress (LOC) (Box 263)
      - Library of Michigan (Box 263)
      - Library Orientation (Box 263)
      - Library Staff Advisory Committee (LSAC)
        - General (Box 263)
        - Elections (Box 263)
      - Life Sciences (Box 263)
      - Making of America (MOA) Celebration
        - General (Box 263)
        - 19th Century Bindings (Box 263)
      - Martin Luther King, Jr. Day (Box 263)
      - Media Union
        - General (Box 263)
        - Executive Committee (Box 263)
      - Michigan Electronic Library (MEL) (Box 263)
      - Michigan Information Transfer Source (MITS) (Box 263)
      - Michigan Library Association (MLA)
        - General (Box 263)
        - Awards (Box 263)
        - Awards Banquet (Box 263)
      - Michigan Library Consortium (MLC) (Box 263)
      - Michigan Research Libraries Triangle (MRLT) (Box 263)
      - MIRLYN Replacement (Box 263)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 263)
      - Music Library (Box 263)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) (Box 263)
      - Online Computer Library Center (OCLC) (Box 263)
      - Papyrology (Box 263)
      - Planning Retreat (Box 263)
      - Preservation/Conservation (Box 263)
      - President (UM) (Box 263)
      - Promotion Review (Box 263)
      - Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (Box 263)
      - Public Goods Council
        - General (Box 263)
        - Alumni Magazine Issue (Box 263)
        - Brochure (Box 263)
        - Mellon Proposal (Box 263)
      - Public Health Library (Box 264)
      - Public Services (Box 264)
      - Rackham Panel: Publishing in the Digital World (Box 264)
      - Research Libraries Group (RLG)
        - General (Box 264)
        - Agreements (Box 264)
        - RLIN (Box 264)
      - Residents (Box 264)
      - Royal Shakespeare Company (RSC) Residency Committee (Box 264)
      - Security Team (Box 264)
      - Selector Forum (Box 264)
      - Shapiro Library (Box 264)
      - Spatial Analysis (Box 264)
      - Special Collections Library (Box 264)
      - Surveys (Box 264)
      - Taubman Medical Library
        - General (Box 264)
        - Renovation (Box 264)
      - Technical Access Systems Services (TASS) (Box 264)
      - Technical and Access Services (TAS) Retreat (Box 264)
      - Travel Committee (Box 264)
      - Uniform Computer Information Transactions Act (UCITA) (Box 264)
      - University Campaign Planning (Box 264)
      - University Press
        - General (Box 264)
        - Executive Committee (Box 264)
        - Finance Subcommittee (Box 264)
      - Visitors (Box 264)
      - Washington, D.C. Alumni Club (Box 264)
      - Whalls Endowment Fund (Box 264)
    - 2001-2002
      - Access ER (electronic records) (Box 264)
      - Acquisitions (Box 264)
      - Amaker, Tommy and Stephanie (Box 264)
      - Appointments (Box 264)
      - Area Programs (Box 264)
      - Assessment (Box 264)
      - Association of Research Libraries (ARL)
        - General, 4 folders (Box 264)
        - Access Committee (Box 264)
        - Membership Meeting Minutes (Box 264)
        - Preservation Studies (Box 264)
        - Reference (Box 264)
        - Scholarly Publishing and Resources Coalition (SPARC) (Box 264)
      - Bentley Historical Library (Box 264)
      - Book Sale (Box 264)
      - Business and Finance Department (Box 264)
      - Cabinet
        - Agendas (Box 264)
        - Minutes (Box 264)
      - Canadian Consulate (Box 264)
      - Center for Research Libraries (CRL) (Box 264)
      - Clements Library: Committee of Management (Box 264)
      - Collection Management and Development Committee/Council (CMDC), 2 folders (Box 265)
      - Collections (Box 265)
      - Collections Faculty Survey (Box 265)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC)
        - General (Box 265)
        - Directors, 2 folders (Box 265)
      - Communications, Public Relations, and Grants (Box 265)
      - Cooperative Access System (CAS) (Box 265)
      - Copyrights (Box 265)
      - Council of State and University Library Directors (COLD) (Box 265)
      - Council on Library and Information Resources (CLIR)
        - Commission on Preservation and Access (CP&A) (Box 265)
        - National Digital Library Federation (NDLF) (Box 265)
      - Development
        - General, 2 folders (Box 265)
        - Library Friends (Box 265)
      - Digital Library Initiative (DLI)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 265)
        - JSTOR (Box 265)
      - Digital Library Services (DLS): LOCKSS (Lots of Copies Keep Stuff Safe) (Box 265)
      - Director's Update (Box 265)
      - Diversity Committee (Box 265)
      - Early English Books Online (EEBO), 2 folders (Box 266)
      - Edwards Brothers (Box 266)
      - Executive Council (Box 266)
      - Facilities (Box 266)
      - Faulkner Conference (Box 266)
      - Field Librarians (Box 266)
      - Government Documents (Box 266)
      - Grievance Procedures (Box 266)
      - Human Resources (HR) (Box 266)
      - Information, School of (SI) (Box 266)
      - Information Technology Division (ITD) (Box 266)
      - Interlibrary Loan (ILL)
        - General (Box 266)
        - Conference (Box 266)
      - International Federation of Library Associations and Institutions (IFLA) (Box 266)
      - Law Library (Box 266)
      - Legal (Box 266)
      - Librarian's Forum (Box 266)
      - Libraries Advisory Committee (LAC) (Box 266)
      - Library Communications Advisory Team (LCAT) (Box 266)
      - Library Council (Box 266)
      - Library Logo (Box 266)
      - Library Logo Mock-ups (Box 266)
      - Library Management System (LMS) (Box 266)
      - Library of Michigan (Box 266)
      - Library Style Guide (Box 266)
      - Library Orientation (Box 266)
      - Library Staff Advisory Committee (LSAC) (Box 266)
      - Life Sciences (Box 266)
      - Media Union
        - General (Box 266)
        - Executive Committee (Box 266)
      - Michigan Academic Library Council (MALC): Strategic Plan (Box 266)
      - Michigan Information Transfer Source (MITS) (Box 266)
      - Michigan Library Association (MLA)
        - General (Box 266)
        - Scholarly Publishing and Resources Coalition (SPARC) Presentation (Box 266)
      - Michigan Library Consortium (MLC) (Box 266)
      - Michigan Research Libraries Triangle (MRLT) (Box 266)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 266)
      - Music Library (Box 266)
      - Online Computer Library Center (OCLC)
        - General (Box 266)
        - Annual Reports (Box 266)
      - Papyrology (Box 266)
      - Preservation/Conservation (Box 266)
      - Printing (Box 266)
      - Promotion Review Committee (PRC) (Box 290)
      - Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (Box 266)
      - Public Goods Council (Box 267)
        - General (Box 267)
        - Mellon Proposal (Box 267)
      - Public Services (Box 267)
      - Reprography Services Task Force (Box 267)
      - Research Libraries Group (RLG)
        - General (Box 267)
        - Agreements (Box 267)
        - Electronic Mail (Box 267)
        - Invoices (Box 267)
      - St. Petersburg (Box 267)
      - Scholarly Publishing Office (Box 267)
      - Senate, University of Michigan (Box 267)
      - Shapiro Library (Box 267)
      - Smithsonian Award (Box 267)
      - Social Work Library (Box 267)
      - Special Collections Library (Box 267)
      - Standifer African American Music Collection (Box 267)
      - Strategic Planning (Box 267)
      - Taubman Medical Library (Box 267)
      - Technical Access Systems Services (TASS) (Box 267)
      - Travel Committee (Box 267)
      - Uniform Computer Information Transactions Act (UCITA) (Box 267)
      - Universitas 21 (Box 267)
      - University Press
        - General (Box 267)
        - Executive Committee (Box 267)
        - Finance Subcommittee (Box 267)
      - Vice-President for Research, Office of (OVPR) (Box 267)
    - 2002-2005
      - Administrative Meeting
        - 2003-2004 (Box 267)
        - 2004-2005 (Box 267)
      - Association of Research Libraries (ARL): Mentor (Ven Basco), 2003-2004 (Box 267)
      - Business Administration Library, 2004-2005 (Box 267)